Hey everyone and thanks for listening to
the Grow Your Life podcast. My name is
Jeremiah Kowski and on this podcast I
help coaches, mentors, trainers to scale
their businesses to make more money than
they ever could imagine. Now on this
episode I want to talk about sales and
what brings in the kind of money that
you want to make in your business. I
meet a lot of coaches and mentors. They
got great programs. The people that we
attract in my wealthy coach academy and
in my VIP program are some of the best
that are out there. They really are some
of the best coaches and mentors. And
whether you're just getting started or
not, I can assure you that if you get
into our ecosystem, we help raise you up
and train you up to become the best that
there is to be. Someone who is of
integrity, somebody who produces results
for their clients. And that's the most
important thing is producing results for
your clients. But I want to tell you the
problem is the best coaches on the
planet, they struggle to get sales. They
struggle to actually get people to buy
from them. And the reason why is they
don't understand
what for no fault of their own, but they
just weren't trained in it. What
actually gets people to make a purchase?
And so what actually gets people to make
a purchase is how does somebody feel
inside of them when they think about it?
What is the belief about the
transformation and result that you're
going to deliver? There's a neurological
neurochemistry that happens that when
somebody sees something that they want
to buy and and and here's how I want you
to kind of understand this whenever you
go out there if you're somebody and and
let's say that you go to buy something
that you're excited for. I'm sure we've
all bought things that we're excited to
buy. We've been really itching for.
we've been we've we're we're we're we've
saved up some money and we're ready to
make that purchase.
Um
that's exactly what people experience in
your business if you're a coach or
mentor or trainer is the is that people
don't just flippantly often buy your
courses. Maybe they'll buy something
that's like low ticket or there's not a
lot of entry. But for our flagship
courses, for our programs, if you're
selling them for 500 to a,000, $2,000 or
even if they're $100 to $200 a month,
people make a purchase, even if it's a
free trial. My Wealthy Coach Academy
program has a free 14-day trial that
people can try out. And yet, people
don't even make the leap into that
simply because it's the most valuable
program that's out there. simply because
it's the best coaching program out
there. That doesn't matter to anybody.
That doesn't matter to you who's
listening to this if you're not already
a client of it. Case in point, you're
not a member of our program. Why?
Because there's not a belief that it's
actually going to produce the result for
you that you want.
And that's exactly what it is. Is that
people don't have that feeling of I'm
going to get an outcome that is
different than what I have experienced
so far in my life by purchasing this.
That's the only reason why anybody's not
buying from you. Now, here's what we
found is we find a lot of our clients,
people who follow us and listen to our
podcast and plug into our content, they
eventually come around or they stop
listening to our content because they
realize that by having me come alongside
them to guide them and direct them and
show them exactly what steps to take in
their business, the ROI that's going to
be produced in that, the fact that I'm
going to fight for them and make sure
that they get results, that's going to
produce the results for them. And
listen, if you're watching this right
now and you want to jump into our
Wealthy Coach Academy program, you can
check out a link in the description of
the YouTube content of this or simply
send me a DM on Instagram and let me
know that you want to jump in. Okay?
Just say, "Hey, I want to jump into the
Wealthy Coach Academy program. I was
listening to the podcast. I want to try
it out. I want to try out the 14-day
trial of this." Okay? So, I'd love to
have you do that. And it's exactly the
same for you in your business that
people they make a purchase because
there is a feeling there's a temperature
a buying temperature a internal pressure
of excitement and pleasure that gets
generated that says okay I am going to
get something positive out of this and
it's built on trust the person trusts
you that you are going to deliver that
you are going to create that result for
them. This goes beyond just simply I got
a great piece of information. You have
to strategically
in the mind of your prospect
be building up that buying temperature,
that buying pressure in all of your
interactions. in every interaction that
I have, I am working to and and I'm
literally pulling back the curtain on
this to the point that it may actually
cause me to not get sales because I'm
revealing what it is that I'm doing with
people. Okay? Like, I'm revealing so
much of what I actually do with people
right now in this episode that some
people may not want to work with me
because of it. I'll tell you this
though, uh, it's actually probably
causing some people to want to work with
me more as well because they're re
they're realizing how it all works and
how I reveal all these things to people.
I show exactly behind the curtain
exactly what it takes is that you build
up that buying temperature, that buying
pressure. And there's a way to
communicate when you are speaking, when
you're writing sales copy, when you're
sending emails, and all of the
interactions that you have with people
that builds that up, that increases that
desire, that gets people to want and
desire to work with you more than
anybody else. And here's what it is. is
oftentimes that people are stuck in a
situation in their life doing the same
thing over and over and over again and
they and they just think that there's no
way out. They've tried everything before
and then you come along with a program
that's going to literally solve every
question struggle that they have. You
have the best program that's out there
for them.
And often times they're just going to
say no not right now. Why? because they
are not feeling internally,
wo, I need this. This is going to be the
difference maker for me. This is going
to move me from where I am to where I
finally want to be. That belief is not
there. That belief doesn't exist in
their minds. And so what you have to do
is strategically
in your interactions
increase that buying temperature and
buying pressure. And we do so by helping
reiterate to people what are their goals
and showing them that what we have to
offer is going to produce the result
that they desire. You want to hear what
their desires are. You want to listen
and have them actually tell you what
they are and then you mirror those back
to the person. If you're doing a one to
many model, you're going to be listening
to what the marketplace wants and
mirroring back to them what their
desires are to give them the outcome
that they've been hoping, praying, and
dreaming for based on the struggle that
has been preventing them from getting
there. To show that your solution
is going to resolve
and create flow
and smoothness. You're going to reduce
friction.
There's friction and you're going to oil
up. You're going to lube up like think
about that like like a lubricant. You
are creating a mental lubricant in the
mind of the person to see, okay, I'm not
going to have friction trying to get
from point A to point B. It's going to
be smooth sailing from there. And often
times the reason why people aren't
buying is because imagine that they're
on a ship going from one island to
another. I saw this analogy from
somebody a while back. There's two ships
there. There's two islands.
Island A is where they're at and island
B is where all their hopes and dreams
are. Okay?
In between where they're at and where
they want to be, there are sharkinfested
waters.
And what they think is that you're just
simply going to ask them to go swim with
the sharks. What they need to know is
that you're creating safety to guide and
direct them and take them above the
sharks so they can avoid all of the
dangers to get to that place where they
want to be. And unfortunately, because
people have been burned so much by
coaches, mentors, trainers, courses,
and you have the influx of artificial
intelligence and YouTube that's out
there where people can get content for
free. People are like, "No, I can I can
learn this somewhere else. I can look
this up on YouTube. I can look this up
on chat GBT.
And that's why people don't end up
buying from you or from me or from
anybody whose offerings because they
don't have the internal drive, desire,
and belief that says boom. You know
what? This person's coaching program
is going to get me from point A to point
B better than anything else that's out
there that I've tried or could try in
this next year.
And here's what you want is you want
people to feel
stupid.
It's a harsh word, I know,
for not taking your offer.
And it's not that you say, "Well, you're
going to feel stupid for not taking my
offer." No. But you want them internally
to be like, "Wow, it would be unwise for
me at this point now that I know that
this is going to produce the result to
say no to this offer,
to say no to this coaching program, to
say no to this course
because of what is going to be produced
in it and the fact that I've been
struggling and the fact that this is
literally based on the testimonies and
and and everything that I've heard is
going to produce that result for me."
And so your offer, your sales copy, your
language, that's what persuades and
increases that trust and buying
temperature
is it gets people to go and say, "Okay,
you know what?
If I don't take this offer, I'm going to
regret it."
And then they're going to take action
and they're going to buy from you. And
that, my friends, is what delivers
sales. All of the funnels and strategy
and tech stuff that we do that we put
together,
all of it boils down to that one thing.
Getting people to say, you know what,
this is going to give me what I want.
And I know it is. And so, I'm going to
commit. I'm going to put my credit card
down. I'm going to pay some money to get
that result cuz I want it. And that's
the only thing that gets people to buy
from you. So all of your efforts must do
that. They can't just inform. They can't
just talk about how great it is. You
have to intentionally persuade people.
And how do we do that? By our
communication, by nurturing that
connection in our emails, in our videos.
I make YouTube videos. I make podcast
episodes. I make webinars. I send emails
out. I make content for that specific
purpose of persuading people and showing
them and increasing that buying
temperature to say, "You know what?
Jeremiah's
program actually looks like it's going
to be the best chance out there for me
to succeed. It looks better than
anything else that I've tried. I've
tried everything before, but I think
finally I'm going to get breakthrough if
I work with Jeremiah." And the same for
you that people are going to finally get
breakthrough when they work with you.
All right? So, listen, I'd love to have
you join me in my Wealthy Coach Academy
program. And if you're a mentor, coach,
and and you you have a friend or a
colleague who's struggling with sales,
share this episode with them. Don't hold
this to yourself. Don't be greedy with
it. Share this episode with everybody
you know. And watch what happens when
you start to apply it. This is a skill,
one of the number one skills that you
must learn.
Everything else is secondary to the
ability to actually know how to sell.
It's not about being sleazy. It's not
about being slimy. It's about knowing
how to get people to desire deeper than
they would on their own. There you go.
Getting people to desire deeper than
they would just by themselves sitting
there knowing the information that the
way you communicate increases that drive
and desire in them to make a purchase.
And that happens in our in all of our
different forms of communication that we
do in our business. All right, listen.
This been a great podcast episode. Talk
soon everybody. Have a good one.